<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<questions>
  <question category="1">
    <qid>1</qid>
    <title>Veni, vidi, vici</title>
    <score>10</score>
	<category>Cryptography</category>
    <data> 
	Robert reached the museum and searched everywhere to find anything suspicious and then he saw something written in Latin "Veni,vidi,vici".
	These were the words of Julius Caesar during Battle of Zela.He knew there was something for him at that place and there was a tablet there with a 
	<![CDATA[
    <a href="venividivici.txt" target="blank">file</a>
]]>
 in it which was something gibberish.He realised that this was his first puzzle.Find the flag hidden in the file.
      </data>

  </question>
  
  <question category="1">
    <qid>2</qid>
    <title>Songs of Experience</title>
    <score>20</score>
	<category>Forensics</category>
    <data> 
	After solving the first puzzle a pop-up appeared with the words written "Songs of Experience" and an
	<![CDATA[
    <a href="soe.jpg" target="blank">image</a> 
]]> of a tiger.Robert was clever enough to guess the writer of the book William Blake,but was having a slight trouble in finding the flag.Find the flag in the image .

      </data>
  </question>
  
  <question category="1">
    <qid>3</qid>
    <title>Maths is Fun</title>
    <score>15</score>
	<category>Cryptography</category>
    <data> 
	There was panic in the museum as a bomb started ticking somewhere .Robert hastily went  near a pillar following the ticking sound where there
	was a bomb with a laptop attached which required an integer input.There was a 	<![CDATA[
    <a href="rsa.txt" target="blank">Card</a> 
]]> on the top of laptop addressing Robert.Robert saw the card and entered a number to disarm the bomb.What is the Number?

 
      </data>
  </question>
  
    <question category="1">
    <qid>4</qid>
    <title>Flip it Around</title>
    <score>25</score>
	<category>Cryptography</category>
    <data> 
	A small kid came to Robbie and gave him a
	<![CDATA[
    <a href="Flipitaround.txt" target="blank">Piece of paper</a>
]]>
.Something was written on it but he could not make out what it was.Then the tablet in his hand started flashing the phrase "Flip it Around".
He knew what it meant and started to decode the message on the paper.Then the tablet requested for a password which was the decrypted message .What is
the message.

      </data>
  </question>
  
    <question category="1">
    <qid>5</qid>
    <title>Annotates</title>
    <score>30</score>
	<category>Web Exploitation</category>
    <data> 
	The 
	<![CDATA[
    <a href="ann.htm" target="blank">Website</a> 
]]> of Tryinh Lab appeared on the Tablet showing a popup with Annotates written on it and asking for input.Find the flag.


      </data>
  </question> 
  
    <question category="1">
    <qid>6</qid>
    <title>JavaScrypt</title>
    <score>50</score>
	<category>Web Exploitation</category>
    <data> 
	Another task came on the site with some password required to reach the next puzzle.It had something to do with the Developer options.
	This <![CDATA[
    <a href="javascry.htm" target="blank">webpage</a> 
]]> came on the screen.


      </data>
  </question>
  
    <question category="1">
    <qid>7</qid>
    <title>Hasta La Vista Baby</title>
    <score>70</score>
	<category>Miscellaneous</category>
    <data> 
	Arnold Schwarzenegger one liners comprised the next set of puzzles.The next puzzle was quite interesting.
	It contained a  
	<![CDATA[
    <a href="arnnie.png" target="blank">image</a>
]]>
find the message encoded in the Terminators word.

      </data>
  </question> 
  
    <question category="1">
    <qid>8</qid>
    <title>RSA - 2</title>
    <score>95</score>
	<category>Cryptography</category>
    <data> 
	After solving puzzles for an hour Robert was presented with the video of his girlfriend to convince him that she was well.He was given the last
	puzzle of the night which involved mathematical knowledge and RSA returned once again.A
	<![CDATA[
    <a href="rsa2.txt" target="blank">File</a> 
]]>
was given to find the flag.Enter the message its not a number.

      </data>
  </question>
  
</questions>


